Hi, my name is Peter Parker, you don't
remember me, but we
used to know each other. Something bad was
gonna happen and the
only way to stop it was to make everyone
forget about me
because I'm not just Peter Parker, I'm
Spider Man.
Put your wimp right? Suit yourself! Go
home! And sometimes Spider Man
has to do the hard thing, even if it
breaks Peter Parker's
heart. What is happening to me? Oh, gosh!
Excuse me, Doctor Banner,
I need your help. What do you say your
name was? 15A
is mutating, could be enormously
dangerous. Spiders have three life cycles.
between cycles, it can leave the spider
vulnerable to threats.
We are faced with a danger, but we can't
control. One we
can't even see. Stay out of my way. You
lose, and a
kid. And for those spiders who make it
through, it amounts to
a kind of... ...keeper. Nice flowers. Oh,
they're, uh, housewarming gift. I'm,
uh, MJ. I'm just a neighbor from across
the hall. It's friendly
neighbor.